[

0ut3r Space
===========](https://0ut3r.space/)

On this page you can find **Terms Of Service**, **Privacy Policy** and **Disclaimer**. Mostly stuff that nobody reads. I guess you also don’t give a fu\*k, but it looks good here, I tried to make it as clear as possible.

**Effective Date: 19-03-2018**

**Last Updated: 19-03-2024**

[](#Terms-of-Service "Terms of Service")Terms of Service
========================================================

By using my website, you agree to abide by these terms of service.

1. **Cookies** Website use cookies in accordance with our privacy policy to enhance user experience.
    
2. **License** You may view and print content from 0ut3r.space for personal use only.
    
3. **User Comments** I do not currently accept user comments. Any future comment system will be subject to additional terms.
    
4. **Hyperlinking** You may link to our website, provided the link is not misleading and does not imply sponsorship or endorsement.
    
5. **Content Liability** I am not responsible for content on external websites linking to us.
    
6. **Reservation of Rights** I reserve the right to request removal of any links to our website and to amend these terms at any time.
    
7. **Disclaimer** I do not guarantee the accuracy or availability of information on my website. I am not liable for any loss or damage resulting from the use of my website.
    
8. **Updates** The last update date indicates changes to these terms. I do not send notifications for updates.

[](#Privacy-Policy "Privacy Policy")Privacy Policy
==================================================

1. **Your Privacy Matters** At 0ut3r Space, I value your privacy and I am committed to safeguarding your personally identifiable information collected through our website.
    
2. **Information Collection** I collect non-personally identifying information, such as browser type and visitor behavior, to understand and improve user experience. I also collect IP addresses for visitors, using this data solely for website improvement purposes.
    
3. **Data Security** While I strive to protect all information, I cannot guarantee absolute security due to the nature of internet transmission and storage.
    
4. **Advertisements** There is no advertisement system implemented to the website, no third party cookies related to ads or tracking.
    
5. **External Links** I am not responsible for the privacy practices of external sites linked from our website. We advise reviewing their Privacy Policy and terms of service.
    
6. **Aggregated Statistics** I may collect and publicly display non-personally identifying aggregated statistics about website usage/traffic. No IP addresses are published.
    
7. **Affiliate Disclosure** I use affiliate links and may earn commissions from certain links. This does not affect your purchases or prices.
    
8. **Cookie Usage** Website use cookies to personalize content and store preferences. Users can adjust browser settings to refuse cookies, but some website features may be impacted.
    
9. **Privacy Policy Changes** I may update our Privacy Policy periodically. Visitors are encouraged to review this page regularly for any updates. Continued use of the site constitutes acceptance of any changes.

[](#Disclaimer "Disclaimer")Disclaimer
======================================

The information provided on 0ut3r.space is for general informational purposes only. While I strive to ensure accuracy, I make no representations or warranties of any kind regarding the completeness, accuracy, reliability, or suitability of the information. Your use of the website and reliance on any information is at your own risk.

1. **Consent** By using the Website, you consent to this Disclaimer and agree to its terms. I am not liable for any damages resulting from the use of our Website.
    
2. **External Links Disclaimer** I do not investigate or monitor the accuracy of external links provided on the Website. I am not responsible for the content or reliability of third-party websites linked through my Website.
    
3. **Reviews** Product or service reviews represent the author’s honest opinions. Any discounts or incentives received for reviews will be disclosed. Users should conduct their own due diligence before relying solely on any review provided on this Website.
    
4. **Fair Use Notice** Some content on the Website may be copyrighted material used under “fair use.” Permission from the copyright owner may be required for any use beyond fair use.
    
5. **Personal Responsibility** Your use of the Website and any actions taken are your own responsibility. I am are not liable for any decisions made or actions taken based on the information provided on the Website.
    
6. **Copyright Information** COPYRIGHT ≥2018 0ut3r Space. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.

© 2018-2024 hoek
